{
    "subject": "resource/Otto_H\u00f6lder",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Stuttgart",
    "human_readable": "Otto H\u00f6lder was born in Stuttgart.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9262595772743225,
            "question": "Name the city where Otto H\u00f6lder was born."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9171823263168335,
            "question": "Where was Otto H\u00f6lder born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8615873456001282,
            "question": "In what year was Otto H\u00f6lder born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5706356763839722,
            "question": "What is Otto H\u00f6lder known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5145800113677979,
            "question": "Where did Otto H\u00f6lder live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.405624121427536,
            "question": "What achievements did Otto H\u00f6lder have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3912804424762726,
            "question": "Are there any notable events associated with Otto H\u00f6lder's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3532813787460327,
            "question": "Was Otto H\u00f6lder involved in any major scientific discoveries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.340443879365921,
            "question": "Did Otto H\u00f6lder work in a specific field?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2645924985408783,
            "question": "What is the significance of Otto H\u00f6lder's work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Otto H\u00f6lder was born in Stuttgart.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3827_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Otto H\u00f6lder work in a specific field?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3827_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Otto H\u00f6lder involved in any major scientific discoveries?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3827_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable events associated with Otto H\u00f6lder's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3827_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3827_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3827_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3827_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3827_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3827_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3827_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3827_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3827_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3827_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3827_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Otto H\u00f6lder was born in Stuttgart.\" Specifically, all four text snippets mention his birthplace as Stuttgart, Germany."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}